Why choose iNeuron For Data Science Master Program?	iNeuron is not only a training institute but also comprises of a team of senior data scientists who have multiple years of experience in data science; deep learning; and machine learning and iNeuron is also into product development. Thus we have the capabilities to provide hands-on training to our candidates via in-house project contribution.
Why choose iNeuron?	iNeuron is not only a training institute but also comprises of a team of senior data scientists who have multiple years of experience in data science; deep learning; and machine learning and iNeuron is also into product development. Thus we have the capabilities to provide hands-on training to our candidates via in-house project contribution.
Why choose iNeuron For Data Science?	iNeuron is not only a training institute but also comprises of a team of senior data scientists who have multiple years of experience in data science; deep learning; and machine learning and iNeuron is also into product development. Thus we have the capabilities to provide hands-on training to our candidates via in-house project contribution.
Why choose iNeuron For Deep Learning?	iNeuron is not only a training institute but also comprises of a team of senior data scientists who have multiple years of experience in data science; deep learning; and machine learning and iNeuron is also into product development. Thus we have the capabilities to provide hands-on training to our candidates via in-house project contribution.
Why choose iNeuron For courses?	iNeuron is not only a training institute but also comprises of a team of senior data scientists who have multiple years of experience in data science; deep learning; and machine learning and iNeuron is also into product development. Thus we have the capabilities to provide hands-on training to our candidates via in-house project contribution.
is this course fit for me?	Yes the course is designed to suit the preferences of both freshers as well as working professionals.All the core concepts are taught from the basics to the advanced level.
Do I have to be good in multiple programming languages?	No we train our students in the programming language like Python and R. The class starts from the basics and goes on till the candidate has not mastered the programming language.
After completing the course will I get job opportunities?	Of course we at iNeuron train the candidates according to the industry needs and specification. We also provide minimum of 3 job referrals along with resume building support as well as training on in-house projects and mock interviews.
what is the duration of datascience masters course	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
datascience masters course duration	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
What are the courses?	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
What are the timings and duration for the course?	We have both an online as well as an offline class; available in multiple slots; available for both weekend and weekdays. The support team will soon contact you with all the details.
show the list of courses	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
tell me the courses	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
provide me course details	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
I want to join a courses in ineuron	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
Do I have to bring my laptop to class?	 It is strongly advised that the candidate brings their laptop to class since it is a practical course and a laptop will be required to practice all the instructions provided in the class. Also for machine learning and deep learning model creation you will get GPU access from iNeuron.
What are the eligibility criteria?	We don’t have any eligibility criteria for our programs as we teach from start to end. Thus anybody interested in the course can join
After completing the course will I get the certificate of Completion?	You will be receiving a certificate of completion from iNeuron stating the completion of the course. The certificate has an international validity.
Where will the classes be conducted?	As of now we have multiple locations in Bangalore. Thus training is possible in any center convenient to the candidate and online classes will be conducted on our live platform.
Will I get the same facilities in Online Batches aswell?	Both online as well as offline classes will be getting the same facilities in terms of resume building; mock interview preparations; job opportunities and much more.
What's the refund policy?	Refund will only be given within two weeks of joining the class.
Will I be assisted for Interview Preparation?	After successful completion of the course the candidate will be given multiple rounds of mock interview preparation as well as a minimum of 3 job referrals
Will there be placement opportunities at the end of the course completion?	There will be placement opportunities after completion of the course. We will also be providing a minimum of 3 job referrals.
Will I be getting any Internship opportunities to enhance my skills?	We are a product based company working on 50+ products for both domestic as well as international markets. Thus we provide our candidates the opportunity to work with us and contribute in our in-house projects which will enhance the candidate’s skill sets and knowledge on the subject.
Do I need to buy some other things rather than a laptop? Like online material; books; etc?	NO.Everything will be provided by iNeuron such as Books; Study materials etc.
What if I am having experience of 4+ in any other domain and I opt for the course then will that experience be counted to get the job as a Data Scientist?	We are responsible for building your resume. So a well-structured plan will be drawn out for each candidate resume concerning years of experience; projects and technology.
What is the admission process?	Step 1:- Discussion with the counselor;step 2:- Ask for the demo;step 3:- career goals and objectives;step 4:- enrolment process
Is accommodation provided?	No we don’t provide any such facilities. Although we have contacts with certain vendors and could make arrangements if required by the candidate.
If I am free on someday apart from a class session; can I visit for more support?	Sure. You can visit iNeuron 24/7 and we will be more than happy to help.
What about revisions?	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
What if we miss one class or two	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
What if I have missed a lecture?	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
is there any recordings for the live sessions	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
If I missed some classes; then can it be rescheduled for me?	The recordings for all the classes will be available in the dashboard. The candidate is most welcome to join any of the batches. Also the candidate can reach out for help regarding any issues.
what happens if I miss some of my topics?	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
What if I miss classes?	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
what if we have some problem and we didn't attend class?	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate. And you can ask your doubts in the doubt clearing session as well.
Is mentors will upload video after live class?	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
Will recordings be available to revise some of the sessions?	All sessions will be recorded and will be provided for revision as per the convenience of the candidate.
machine learning course fee	The course fees for various courses are as follows:Data Science Masters: INR 40000 +GST;Machine Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;Deep Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;NLP Masters: INR 3000 +GST
what is fee for nlp masters	The course fees for various courses are as follows:Data Science Masters: INR 40000 +GST;Machine Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;Deep Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;NLP Masters: INR 3000 +GST
what is the fees structure	The course fees for various courses are as follows:Data Science Masters: INR 40000 +GST;Machine Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;Deep Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;NLP Masters: INR 3000 +GST
fees?	The course fees for various courses are as follows:Data Science Masters: INR 40000 +GST;Machine Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;Deep Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;NLP Masters: INR 3000 +GST
What is the next batch schedule?	An email with your details have already been sent to the support team. They are going to contact you soon.
What is the course fees?	The course fees for various courses are as follows:Data Science Masters: INR 40000 +GST;Machine Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;Deep Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;NLP Masters: INR 3000 +GST
course fees?	The course fees for various courses are as follows:Data Science Masters: INR 40000 +GST;Machine Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;Deep Learning Masters: INR 3000 +GST;NLP Masters: INR 3000 +GST
What about job?	We'll provide referral to the candidates. We have our own custom portal where you can search for jobs.The link is:  https://jobs.ineuron.ai
What about placement assistance?	We'll provide referral to the candidates. We have our own custom portal where you can search for jobs.The link is:  https://jobs.ineuron.ai
What about job support	We'll provide referral to the candidates. We have our own custom portal where you can search for jobs.The link is:  https://jobs.ineuron.ai
I want to take a demo class	There  won't be a separate demo class for individual candidate. However you can check our youtube channel for class recordings and you'll have a fair idea of our teaching methods.YouTube Link: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb1GdqUqArXMQ3RS86lqqOw/videos
In which domain we will get projects	We have projects with almost all the prominent idustry domains like insurane;healthcare;Banking & Finance; Security and Survellance etc.
List of projects	Many industry level projects shall be discussed in the class and many shall be given to you to solve on your own
Which projects will be discussed?	Many industry level projects shall be discussed in the class and many shall be given to you to solve on your own
What is the course duration?	The list of the courses and durations for various courses are:Data Science Masters:  6 Months course+ 3 Months Projects;Machine Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;Deep Learning Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions;NLP Masters: 4 Months course+ Project Discussions
What about doubt clearing?	Support after class shall be provided in terms of doubt clearing; different software installation or any other course-related issue that you might face during the course.There will be dedicated doubt clearing sessions. You can send email to instructors from the student dashboard as well.
How are we going to clear our doubts?	Support after class shall be provided in terms of doubt clearing; different software installation or any other course-related issue that you might face during the course.There will be dedicated doubt clearing sessions. You can send email to instructors from the student dashboard as well.
What if we have doubts?	Support after class shall be provided in terms of doubt clearing; different software installation or any other course-related issue that you might face during the course.There will be dedicated doubt clearing sessions. You can send email to instructors from the student dashboard as well.
What about after class support?	Support after class shall be provided in terms of doubt clearing; different software installation or any other course-related issue that you might face during the course.There will be dedicated doubt clearing sessions. You can send email to instructors from the student dashboard as well.
What if I am not comfortable with the timings and I want to change the batch?	You can contact the support team. They’ll assist you in getting different batch.
What are the EMI options available?	"An EMI option is available only for the Data Science masters course. You can avail a Zero Cost EMI for 6 months if ;1)	You live in any of the 5 cities: New Delhi; Mumbai; Kolkata; Bangalore; Chennai.;2)	You have an HDFC or ICICI credit card.;3)            You have a monthly income more than INR 15000"
What is the cut-off to get a certificate?	A certificate is issued to the candidates scoring at least an overall 60 %. 
Will you provide support for my own custom project?	Yes. We’ll be more than willing to help you with all the hurdles.
Do you help us in resume building?	Yes. We’ll help you build your resume based on the domain you have already worked in.
Will you help with my resume preparation and discussion?	Yes. We’ll help you build your resume based on the domain you have already worked in.
What are the internship opportunities?	Both paid and unpaid internships are available with us. The selection for the internship will solely depend on your interview result.
Do you provide internship opportunities?	Both paid and unpaid internships are available with us. The selection for the internship will solely depend on your interview result.
Can I get an internship after the course completion?	Both paid and unpaid internships are available with us. The selection for the internship will solely depend on your interview result.
What about interview preparation?	We’ll have at least 3 Mock interviews for each candidate to prepare them for a job interview.
Do you help with interview preparations?	We’ll have at least 3 Mock interviews for each candidate to prepare them for a job interview.
Are there any mock interview sessions?	We’ll have at least 3 Mock interviews for each candidate to prepare them for a job interview.
Fees concession?	No. Currently we are not offering any scholarships.
Is any discount?	No. Currently we are not offering any scholarships.
any discount	No. Currently we are not offering any scholarships.
Any concession	No. Currently we are not offering any scholarships.
Do you provide scholarship as well?	No. Currently we are not offering any scholarships.
Are there any scholarships available?	No. Currently we are not offering any scholarships.
What will be the level of the course?	The course caters to the needs of both absolute beginners and the knowledged ones. We’ll start from scratch and then take it to the level where the candidates are ready for job interviews.
Is this course sufficient for getting a job?	The syllabus of the course covers all the concepts which are required for cracking an interview and landing a job.
What are the skills required for a data scientist?	"The primary skills are:1.	Basic analytical ability;2.	A mathematical approach to the problem at hand;3.	EDA to build intuition from data;4.	Concepts of deep learning ;5.	Concepts of NLP;6.	Model deployments"
How will I do a transition from my current field to data science?	We’ll help you to showcase relevant projects based on your previous experience and help you with resume and interview preparation. With all this you’ll definitely be in a position to change jobs.
How will you help with my career transition?	We’ll help you to showcase relevant projects based on your previous experience and help you with resume and interview preparation. With all this you’ll definitely be in a position to change jobs.
I am from different background. Is data science masters course good for me or not	We’ll help you to showcase relevant projects based on your previous experience and help you with resume and interview preparation. With all this you’ll definitely be in a position to change jobs.
Is it possible to do a career transition if I have work experience in another domain?	We’ll help you to showcase relevant projects based on your previous experience and help you with resume and interview preparation. With all this you’ll definitely be in a position to change jobs.
What are the prerequisites for attending this course?	There are no prerequisites as such. We’ll start from scratch assuming that the candidates are entirely new to the filed and then we’ll build the concepts from the beginning itself.
Which programming language are you using for the course?	This course is conducted in python 3.X version.
In which language the course is taught?	This course is conducted in python 3.X version.
Are you going to use Python or R?	This course is conducted in python 3.X version.
Why are you using Python instead of R for this course?	Python is used because it has a more extensive set of libraries for both Machine Learning and Deep Learning compared to R.
Is a mathematical background required for taking the course?	A mathematical background is not required. We’ll explain all the mathematics involved thoroughly.
What is the mathematical background needed for the course?	A mathematical background is not required. We’ll explain all the mathematics involved thoroughly.
Do I need a degree in Statistics to become a data scientist?	A degree in statistics is not mandatory to become a data scientist.
What is the course Structure?	The assumption for the course is that the attendees do not know programming at all. We’ll start right from the scratch for all the concepts.
what is ML master course structure?	The assumption for the course is that the attendees do not know programming at all. We’ll start right from the scratch for all the concepts.
how are the courses designed?	The assumption for the course is that the attendees do not know programming at all. We’ll start right from the scratch for all the concepts.
Is previous programming experience required for attending the course?	The assumption for the course is that the attendees do not know programming at all. We’ll start right from the fundamental of programming.
Do I need to be good at programming to attend the course?	The assumption for the course is that the attendees do not know programming at all. We’ll start right from the fundamental of programming.
What are the deployment topics covered?	"We shall cover deployment to the following Cloud service providers:1.	Google Cloud Platform;2.	Microsoft Azure;3.	AWS;4.	Pivotal;5.	Heroku "
What algorithms are part of the course?	The list of the algorithms is already mentioned in the syllabus already sent to you. We’ll cover all the industry-leading algorithm s and libraries.
Which algorithms are you going to cover?	The list of the algorithms is already mentioned in the syllabus already sent to you. We’ll cover all the industry-leading algorithm s and libraries.
Is a Masters or Doctorate required to become a data scientist?	There are no such requirements. The selection shall depend on your performance in the interview.
Is an M.Tech or PhD required to become a data scientist?	There are no such requirements. The selection shall depend on your performance in the interview.
How many hours do I need to study daily?	The learning rate varies from person to person. But around 2 hours daily shall suffice.
Which course should I take first? ML or DL?	Our suggestion would be to cover ML first and then go for DL. But there is no such dependency. You can take the course in any order.
How is iNeuron different from others?	"Following are the reasons that set us apart:1.	The quality of the content delivered. You won’t find many of the contents that we teach with any of our contemporaries.;2.	We teach till production deployment- Our USP;3.	We’ll help you even with your custom projects;4.	We’ll conduct mock interviews and resume discussion for each of the candidates based on their skills- an industry first.;5.	We provide job alerts and referrals.;6.	We provide internship opportunities.;7.	And the list just goes on…"
First I should go for Machine learning or Deep learning?	Our suggestion would be to cover ML first and then go for DL. But there is no such dependency. You can take the course in any order.
How are you better than other institutes?	Our suggestion would be to cover ML first and then go for DL. But there is no such dependency. You can take the course in any order.
What is better? ML masters or DL masters?	Our suggestion would be to cover ML first and then go for DL. But there is no such dependency. You can take the course in any order.
if i want to join offline?	We have both online and offline batches. You can join any one of them as per your convenience.
if i want to join online?	We have both online and offline batches. You can join any one of them as per your convenience.
Are there any offline batches?	We have both online and offline batches. You can join any one of them as per your convenience.
Are there any online batches?	We have both online and offline batches. You can join any one of them as per your convenience.
Tell me about iNeuron?	iNeuron provides the best service to our clients in terms of product development. Similarly providing the best education to our beloved students we are here to drive a positive change in the best interest of all.
Is it an actual company or fake?	We have a proven track record. iNeuron provides the best service to our clients in terms of product development. Similarly providing the best education to our beloved students we are here to drive a positive change in the best interest of all.
What does iNeuron do?	iNeuron provides the best service to our clients in terms of product development. Similarly providing the best education to our beloved students we are here to drive a positive change in the best interest of all.
What is deep learning masters?	An email has been sent to the Support Team with your contact information. You'll be contacted soon.
What is Machine learning masters?	An email has been sent to the Support Team with your contact information. You'll be contacted soon.
How many classes will be there in a week?	Weekly there shall be 3 classes. 2 Theory and 1 doubt clearing
How many classes will be there per week?	Weekly there shall be 3 classes. 2 Theory and 1 doubt clearing
Is there any installment?	"An EMI option is available only for the Data Science masters course. You can avail a Zero Cost EMI for 6 months if 1)	You live in any of the 5 cities: New Delhi; Mumbai; Kolkata; Bangalore; Chennai.;2)	You have an HDFC or ICICI credit card.;3)            You have a monthly income more than INR 15000"
What about installments?	"An EMI option is available only for the Data Science masters course. You can avail a Zero Cost EMI for 6 months if 1)	You live in any of the 5 cities: New Delhi; Mumbai; Kolkata; Bangalore; Chennai.;2)	You have an HDFC or ICICI credit card.;3)            You have a monthly income more than INR 15000"
Can we pay course fee through installments?	"An EMI option is available only for the Data Science masters course. You can avail a Zero Cost EMI for 6 months if 1)	You live in any of the 5 cities: New Delhi; Mumbai; Kolkata; Bangalore; Chennai.;2)	You have an HDFC or ICICI credit card.;3)            You have a monthly income more than INR 15000"
what about projects?	Many industry level projects shall be discussed in the class and many shall be given to you to solve on your own
Who will be our mentors?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
who will take the classes?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
Who will be taking the classes?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
Who will be teaching the batches?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
what about mentors or teachers?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
who takes the batches for Deep Learning?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
Who will takethe  classes for DL masters?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
who takes the classes for Deep Learning?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
who takes the batches for DL?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
who takes the classes for DL?	We have various well qualified SMEs who are real life data scientists. They will be taking your classes
Are the courses Online or offline?	We have both online and offline batches as per your need.
Are the batches Online or offline?	We have both online and offline batches as per your need.
Online teaching mode or offline teaching?	We have both online and offline batches as per your need.
timing for weekday batches	We have sent an email to the support team. They are going to contact you with all these details
what is timing for weekday batches	We have sent an email to the support team. They are going to contact you with all these details
what are the timings of courses?	We have sent an email to the support team. They are going to contact you with all these details
what are the timings of the batches?	We have sent an email to the support team. They are going to contact you with all these details
what about course timings?	We have sent an email to the support team. They are going to contact you with all these details
What are the other things we can get from this course	1. You'll get free lifetime acces to the material.;2. Live mentoring and doubt clearing;3. Recorded sessions in your dashboard if you miss the class;4. Industry project discussions;5. Resume Preparation;6. Moc interviews
what are the payment options?	You can pay in full or in installments based on the course that you select. You'll get a call from the support tem soon.After your conversation with our support team you'll get a payment link. You can click that link and do the payment.
Where we have to pay?	You can pay in full or in installments based on the course that you select. You'll get a call from the support tem soon.After your conversation with our support team you'll get a payment link. You can click that link and do the payment.
what if i want to stop attending the course	A refund is only provided till one month of joining
how many members are going to join	For the affordable AI courses the strength generally is around 800. For Datascience masters the stenth is not more than 50
What will be the number of people in the batch?	For the affordable AI courses the strength generally is around 800. For Datascience masters the stenth is not more than 50
What will be the number of people in the course?	For the affordable AI courses the strength generally is around 800. For Datascience masters the stenth is not more than 50
batch strength?	For the affordable AI courses the strength generally is around 800. For Datascience masters the stenth is not more than 50
Did we need to learn statistics as well?	Yes a basic understandinhg of the Mathematical concepts is necessary for understanding the algorithms.
What is the process of joining offline courses?	An email with your details have already been sent to the support team. They are going to contact you soon with all the information.
What is the process of joining online courses?	An email with your details have already been sent to the support team. They are going to contact you soon with all the information.
How to join online batch?	An email with your details have already been sent to the support team. They are going to contact you soon with all the information.
How to join offline batch?	An email with your details have already been sent to the support team. They are going to contact you soon with all the information.
you will develop our resume?	We are responsible for building your resume. So a well-structured plan will be drawn out for each candidate resume concerning years of experience; projects and technology.
Will you help with my resume building	We are responsible for building your resume. So a well-structured plan will be drawn out for each candidate resume concerning years of experience; projects and technology.
what about interviews?	We'll conduct atleast 3 mock interviews for candidates just like the original job interview.
Do you conduct inerview sessions also?	We'll conduct atleast 3 mock interviews for candidates just like the original job interview.
Which mode is good? Online or offline?	Both the modes have equal quality of the content delivered. As per your convenience you can choose any of those.
What is good? Online or offline?	Both the modes have equal quality of the content delivered. As per your convenience you can choose any of those.
to whom i can ask my study related doubts?	There will be dedicated doubt clearing session for each of the batches for live doubt clearing. You can share your screen and ask your queries. You can also send your queries from the student dashboard
who will clear our doubts?	There will be dedicated doubt clearing session for each of the batches for live doubt clearing. You can share your screen and ask your queries. You can also send your queries from the student dashboard
How will the doubt clearing session take place?	There will be dedicated doubt clearing session for each of the batches for live doubt clearing. You can share your screen and ask your queries. You can also send your queries from the student dashboard
why other courses are for 3k and data science masters is for 40k	Because the DSM course has only 40-50 students. So the attention to individual candidates is more. And it is a combination of all the courses that we provide.
why nlp masters is so cheap compared to datascience masters	Because the DSM course has only 40-50 students. So the attention to individual candidates is more. And it is a combination of all the courses that we provide.
why other courses are for 3000 rupees and data science masters is for 40000 Rupees?	Because the DSM course has only 40-50 students. So the attention to individual candidates is more. And it is a combination of all the courses that we provide.
if i don't have time now but i want to join it later?	Yes you can. The team will reachout to you and you can discuss your schedule with them.
I want to join next month. Do I have to pay same money	Yes. The fees won't change.
how much gst we have to pay?	The GST is 18 % as per the Government Regulations
How much GST is being charged?	The GST is 18 % as per the Government Regulations
What is the GST in course fee?	The GST is 18 % as per the Government Regulations
Is python a tough language?	When compared to other programming languages Python is a bit easier to understand
what about case studies	All the details are there in the syllabus sent to you. You can visit this link as well: https://ux.ineuron.ai/casestudies.php
Do you provide case studies too?	All the details are there in the syllabus sent to you. You can visit this link as well: https://ux.ineuron.ai/casestudies.php
Where is the office located	Our Head Office is in Bangalore India. Please check our website for the complete address
send me the location of the office	Our Head Office is in Bangalore India. Please check our website for the complete address
show me the curriculum for data science masters	An email with all the details have been sent to your email.
show me the curriculum	An email with all the details have been sent to your email.
Show me the syllabus	An email with all the details have been sent to your email.
when is the next batch starting?	An email has been sent to the Support Team with your contact information. You'll be contacted soon.
What is the schedule for next batch?	An email has been sent to the Support Team with your contact information. You'll be contacted soon.
do you provide any study materials	Yes. All the matreials and assignments will be uploaded to your dashboard.
do you provide any course materials	Yes. All the matreials and assignments will be uploaded to your dashboard.
i want some time to think about joining	Please take your time. The support team will be in touch with you.
when i can join the course	The support team is going to call you soon with all the details
can i join the course?	Yes. The support team is going to call you soon.
What is the procedure to join the course?	The support team is going to call you soon with all the details
I don't want to join the course	It's Okay. The support team will call you to get a feedback.
classes will be in morning or evening?	We have both the options. The suuport team is soon going to call you and your dquestions shall  be answered.
is there any additional fees	No. There are no hidden charges.
Are you going to charge anything extra?	No. There are no hidden charges.
I have a doubt regarding fee	The support team is going to call you soon. You can ask them all your doubts.
I have some queries about fees	The support team is going to call you soon. You can ask them all your doubts.
Do we have any assignments and projects	Yes there are a lot of assignments and projects in all the courses.
Do we have hands on sessions	The curriclulum is explained using hands-on codes.
